

Patrick Dobranowski

VICE PRESIDENT OF ENGINEERING AT DUPPER ANALYTICS | SOFTWARE ENGINEER | FULL STACK DEVELOPER | ENTREPRENEUR

PROFILE

Self-employed app, software, web, and game developer for many years in Middle School and High School who began working as a Software Engineer and Full-Stack for Dupper Analytics as their Vice President of Engineering and Co-Founder during Junior Year of High School. Founder of two other companies - Untitled and Untitled -(LLC) developing software and websites in student connections/education and game design/entertainment respectively. Also, an avid competitor in many STEM-based competitions and hackathons including being captain of a CTF team that placed 9th Nationally in Carnegie Mellon's PicoCTF, Founder, President, and Captain of a Platinum Division ranked team in CyberPatriot from Rock Canyon High School, National Scholar with Honors status receiver from 10th place at the National Cyber Scholarship Foundation Cybersecurity Competition, receiver of a Top 3 finalist ranking at Technology Student's Association Nationals, Top 3 finalist ranking in State-Level Science Olympiad, Gold Division Level USACO member, and avid Speech and Debate Enthusiast.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Birth date

02/25/2004

Nationality

United States, Poland

Address

6301 Ellingwood Point Place Castle Rock, CO 80108 USA

CONTACT

- patrick.dobranowski@gmail.com patrick@dupperanalytics.com
- (720)-448-7515
- zerodaytea.github.io
- Patrick Dobranowski
- ZeroDayTea

WORK EXPERIENCE

Vice President of Engineering | Co-Founder

2021-Now **DUPPER ANALYTICS**

Vice President of Engineering at Dupper Analytics developing the Dupper Analytics Cloud-Based Solutions product as a Software Engineer and Full-Stack Developer who worked with several clients and effectively created, tested, and deployed cloud-based solutions to business' data analytics problems and aided them in navigating an increasingly data-driven world. Worked heavily with PHP, Python, SQL, HTML, CSS, and client networking to create a modern and easy-to-use product helping companies track, log, and analyze their data which ended up increasing profitability in numerous clients.

CEO | Founder

UNTITLED 2020-Now

Software Developer and Full-Stack Developer who created a platform for student connections and interest in Computer Science that not only connected middle school, high school, and college-level students with computer science opportunities and competitions around them but also provided education and in-person tutoring services to educate them in computer science related topics.

CEO | Founder

2020-Now

Created, developed, tested, and released entertaining video games for Steam on PC platforms, iOS, and Android. Most notable project was "Untitled", a procedurally generated action-adventure game focused on

Aerospace Engineering, Computer Science, Cybersecurity Intern

COLORADO SPACE BUSINESS ROUNDTABLE

2020-2020

Intern at the Colorado Space Business Roundtable with experience working with local industry professionals such as Lockheed Martin and Boeing in Aerospace Engineering, Computer Science, and Cybersecurity.

EDUCATION

Computer Science Foundations Certification

2021 SANS INSTITUTE

Dual-Enrollment | 4.0/4.0 GPA

ARAPAHOE COMMUNITY COLLEGE

2019-Now

DUAL-ENROLLMENT COURSES TAKEN:

- -CALCULUS III MAT203
- -INTRODUCTION TO BIOTECHNOLOGY BIO160
- High School Diploma | 4.43 GPA

ROCK CANYON HIGH SCHOOL

2018-Now

ACTIVITIES:

- -CYBER PATRIOT (FOUNDER OF SCHOOL ACTIVITY AND PRESIDENT IN PLATINUM DIVISION)
- -TECHNOLOGY STUDENT ASSOCIATION (OFFICER AND TOP 3 AT NATIONAL-LEVEL COMPETITION)
- -SCIENCE OLYMPIAD (PLACEMENT AT TOP 3 AT STATE-LEVEL COMPETITION)
- HONORS SOCIETIES:

-SPEECH AND DEBATE

- -NATIONAL HONORS SOCIETY -MU ALPHA THETA MATH HONORS SOCIETY
- -SOCIEDAD HONORIA HISPANICA

TOP COURSES TAKEN

Calculus III - MAT203	Introduction to Biotechnology - BIO160			Calculus B	ic .
AP Computer Science A	AP Physics 1 & 2	AP Span	ish Language	AP Lan	guage and Composition
AP United States History	AP Environmental Science		AP European History		AP Human Geography









BUSINESS



LANGUAGES

- English Native proficiency
- Polish Native Proficiency
- Spanish Full Professional Proficiency

HONORS & AWARDS

- Carnegie Mellon's PicoCTF Top 10 National Finalist: https://cylab.cmu.edu/news/2021/04/23picoCTF2021.html
- National Cyber Scholarship Foundation Top 10 "National Scholar With Honors" Scholarship
- Technology Student's Association National Top 3 Finalist
- Cyber Patriot Platinum Division Finalist
- USACO Gold Level Member
- Science Olympiad Top 3 State Finalist